

# Komara Indra Putra

Computer Science Student

- **Q** 081339879657
- ★ komaraindra21@gmail.com
- komaraip.github.io
- Jakarta, Indonesia

#### SUMMARY

Hello! I'm currently in my second year at BINUS University, where I'm wholeheartedly pursuing a major in Computer Science. I'm an activist of HIMTI, where I've dived into web development and event organization. These experiences have taught me valuable technical skills and the art of teamwork. I believe in the power of technology and collaboration to drive innovation.

# EXPERIENCE

#### Staff at Operator Division

03/2024 - Present

BVoice Radio <sup>对</sup>

# Staff at Response Division

03/2023 - Present

HIMTI BINUS University ₹

- · Make video based learning and summary for several courses.
- Be the person in charge of the summary group for several courses.

### **Event Staff at HIVENT 2023**

09/2023 - 10/2023

HIMTI BINUS University ↗

- Make rundown and event concept.
- Be the person in charge of the game at the event.

#### Mentor at SESKAM 2023

09/2023 - 10/2023

- HIMTI BINUS University ↗
- Introduce HIMTI for candidate activists.
- Guide 20+ candidate activists during events that will equip them with basic organizational skills.

# Website Development Staff at TECHFEST 2023

04/2023 - 07/2023

- HIMTI BINUS University ₹
- Create responsive web layouts that adapt to various screen sizes and devices.
- Collaborate with CnD (Creative and Design) staff to implement UI elements, ensuring a seamless transition from design prototypes to the final web application.

# EDUCATION

Computer Science BINUS University 09/2022 - Present

SKILLS

HTML Expert PHP Intermediate
CSS Advanced Javascript Intermediate